Guide to the Stanford University, School of Humanities and Sciences, Innovative Academic Courses, Records
Stanford University. Libraries.
- Records, Accession ARCH-1992-086
  - Boyle, Father Eugene (Box 7, Folder 30)
  - Brower, David (Box 7, Folder 31)
  - Bube, Richard (Box 7, Folder 32)
  - Evaluations Buika, Robert J (Box 7, Folder 33)
  - Byerwalter, Marianne (Box 7, Folder 34)
  - Coughlin, Walter (Box 7, Folder 35)
  - Cartun, Ari Mark (Box 7, Folder 36)
  - Cheever, Fred (Box 7, Folder 37)
  - Chenevert, David (Box 7, Folder 38)
  - Davies, Todd (Box 7, Folder 39)
  - Chenevert and Moore, Jim (Box 7, Folder 40)
  - Evaluations Citron, Chaim (Box 7, Folder 41)
  - Cohen, Brad and Lynch, Janet (Box 7, Folder 42)
  - Cole, Wendell (Box 7, Folder 43)
  - Coombs, Julie (Box 7, Folder 44)
  - Correl, Sylvia et al (Box 7, Folder 45)
  - Davis, Brent (Box 7, Folder 46)
  - Evaluations Timothy Davis (1979-1980) Deceased (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Diogenes, Marvin (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Evaluations Sarah Donnelly (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Felt, Douglas (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Evaluations Duca, George (1976-1981) (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Ely, Marc (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Essey, Tina (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Ellsberg, Daniel (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Feliz, Margot (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Forte, Dan (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Galton, Julie (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Garcia, Frank (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Gavin, Cristina M. (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Genser, Josh (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Gilinsky, Armand (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Giguere, Robert (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Gioia, Ted (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Graebner, Michael (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - Evaluations Gregory, George (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - Hahn, Thomas (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - Hammond, Mike (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - Harris, Robin (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - Hartwell, Andrew (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - Heck, R.C. Devon (Box 8, Folder 24)
  - Heinz (Box 8, Folder 25)
  - Evaluations, Heslop, Jacqueline (Box 8, Folder 26)
  - Evaluations, Hilton, Ronald (Box 8, Folder 27)
  - Huang, Milton (Box 8, Folder 28)
  - Jacobstein, Myron (Box 8, Folder 29)
  - Killas, Harry (Box 8, Folder 30)
  - Korine, Harry D. (Box 8, Folder 31)
  - Krass, Jonathan (Box 8, Folder 32)
  - Krass, Jonathan (Box 8, Folder 33)
  - Krumboltz, Helen (Box 8, Folder 34)
  - Lanza, Michael (Box 8, Folder 35)
  - Evaluations Lawry, Steve and Erica (Box 8, Folder 36)
  - Lebovitz, Stephen (Box 8, Folder 37)
  - Lempert, David (Box 8, Folder 38)
  - Levin, Yosef L. (Box 8, Folder 39)
  - Undergraduate Special Course Evaluations Martoff, CJ and Finston, R (Box 8, Folder 40)
  - Lobsenz, James (Box 8, Folder 41)
  - Evalutations, Hugh Macdonald (1977-1980) (Box 8, Folder 42)
  - Mandel, Geoffrey (Box 8, Folder 43)
  - Mc Colgan, William N. (Box 8, Folder 44)
  - Mc Nichols, John (Box 8, Folder 45)
  - Evaluations, Meads, Kent, and Prudek, Fred (Box 8, Folder 46)
  - Montgomery, Will (Box 8, Folder 47)
  - Nabti, Pat (Box 8, Folder 48)
  - Orsak, M (Box 8, Folder 49)
  - Evaluations, Nigro, Louis (Box 8, Folder 50)
  - Noji, Eria (Box 8, Folder 51)
  - Evaluations, Nold, Ellen (Box 8, Folder 52)
  - Evaluations, Novick, Lee (Box 8, Folder 53)
  - Rights of Animals Chris Ozeroff (Box 8, Folder 54)
  - Payne, Peter (Box 8, Folder 55)
  - Penrose, James D. (Box 8, Folder 56)
  - Evaluations Piziali, Kathy (Box 8, Folder 57)
  - Pulvers, Marty (Box 8, Folder 58)
  - Rodgers, Marcie (Box 8, Folder 59)
  - Serbein, Oscar (Box 8, Folder 60)
  - Evaluations, Saffle, Susan (Box 8, Folder 61)
  - Saxenian (Box 8, Folder 62)
  - Simon, W Scott (Box 8, Folder 63)
  - Evaluations, Shepherd, Scott (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Shanker, Sandra (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Shenberg, Galia (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Smith, Jennifer (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Standing, Beverly (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Stone, David J (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Student Pub (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Wahid, Taha, Spring 1977 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Nicholas Thacher (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Thacher, Nicholas, A. (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Thiemann, Micheal (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Tucci, Christopher (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Tomich, Laurie and Perry Paige (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - #36 Celestial Navigation Van Heeckeren, Jake Winter, 1974-1975 (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Steven Vineberg (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - Wagstaffe, James M. (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - Winborne (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - Yarak, Dennis (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - Undergraduate Special: Courses (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - Autumn Quarter Courses 1972-1973 (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - Unfiled Evaluations from Spring 1973-1974 (Box 9, Folder 21)
  - Ellsberg MQE, Spring 1979 (Box 9, Folder 22)
  - UGS Proposals Winter 1987 (Box 9, Folder 23)
  - Course Proposals Autumn 1987-1988 (Box 9, Folder 24)
  - Course Ideas Winter 1992 (Box 9, Folder 25)
  - Course Development Winter 1988 (Box 9, Folder 26)
  - Course Development Spring 1988 (Box 9, Folder 27)
  - Course Development (Box 9, Folder 28)
  - UGS One Unit Class Ideas (Box 9, Folder 29)
  - UGS Grading Patterns (Box 9, Folder 30)
  - UGS Stafs (Box 9, Folder 31)
  - UGS Proposals (Box 9, Folder 32)
  - Handbooks (Box 9, Folder 33)
  - Undergraduate Specials Policy (Box 9, Folder 34)
  - Undergraduate Specials Distribution Lists (Box 9, Folder 35)
  - Undergraduate Specials Guidelines (Box 9, Folder 36)
  - ASSU Course Review (Box 9, Folder 37)
  - Undergraduate Specials Course Evaluations (Box 9, Folder 38)
  - Undergraduate Specials Guidelines and CUS Actions (Box 9, Folder 39)
  - FS Proposal Replies, 1971-1972 (Box 9, Folder 40)
  - Winter 1970-1971 (Box 9, Folder 41)
  - Spring 1970-1971 (Box 9, Folder 42)
  - Summer School 1970-1971 (Box 9, Folder 43)
  - UGS Application 1971-1972 (Box 9, Folder 44)
  - Undergraduate Specials Application Forms (Box 9, Folder 45)
  - Autumn Quarter 1971-1972 (Box 9, Folder 46)
  - Winter Quarter 1971-1972 (Box 9, Folder 47)
  - Spring Quarter 1971-1972 (Box 9, Folder 48)
  - Chronological File Through 1/30/72 (Box 9, Folder 49)
  - Freshman Seminar Proposal Responses 1972-1973 (Box 9, Folder 50)
  - Honors Tutorial Program and Other Tutorials (Box 9, Folder 51)
  - Seminars for Entering Student Community, 1973-1974 (Box 9, Folder 52)
  - EDP Credit and the Arts (Box 9, Folder 53)
  - Undergraduate Special Program 1971-1974 (Box 9, Folder 54)
  - Freshman Seminars (Box 9, Folder 55)
  - Seminars for Entering Students 1975-1976 (Box 9, Folder 56)
  - UGS 1974-1975 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Seminars for Entering Students 1976-1977 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Extra Departmental Programs Brochures (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Proposals: 1977-1978 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Undergraduate Special Course Admin. 1974-1975 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - End Quarter Reports Winter 1981-1982 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Undergraduate Special Program Administration 1975-1976 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - End Quarter Reports Summer 1982 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Grade Reports, Fall 1982-1983 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - End Quarter Reports, Winter Quarter 1982-1983 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - End Quarter Evaluations, Spring 1982-1983 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - End Quarter Reports Fall 1983-1984 (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - End Quarter Reports Winter 1983-1984 (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - End Quarter Reports Spring 1983-1984 (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - End Quarter Reports Summer Quarter, 1983-1984 (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - End Quarter Reports, Winter 1984-1985 (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - End Quarter Reports, Spring 1984-1985 (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - End Quarter Reports, Fall 1984-1985 (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - Summer 1985 (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - UGS Bulletin of Courses 1985-1986 (Box 10, Folder 20)
  - Cue Charge: January 1964 (Box 10, Folder 21)
  - Racism Group Course Comm. on Undergrad Education (Box 10, Folder 22)
  - Undergraduate Special Program Administration Fall 1969 (Box 10, Folder 23)
  - Undergraduate Special Course Administration, 1968 (Box 10, Folder 24)
  - Undergraduate Specials: Course Administration 1968-1969 (Box 10, Folder 25)
  - Short Term Teaching Appointments (Box 10, Folder 26)
  - Undergraduate Specials Administration Winter 1969-1970 (Box 10, Folder 27)
  - Undergraduate Specials Administration Spring 1970 (Box 10, Folder 28)
  - Subcommittee: Extra-Dept. Courses Administration: Spring 1970 (Box 10, Folder 29)
  - Subcommittee- Extra-Dept. Courses Minutes Spring 1970 (Box 10, Folder 30)
  - Subcommittee on Extradepartmental Courses, C-US 1970-1971 (Box 10, Folder 31)
  - Undergraduate Special Administration Fall 1970 (Box 10, Folder 32)
  - Undergraduate Special Program Administration Fall 1970 (Box 10, Folder 33)
  - Undergraduate Special Course Administration 1970-1971 (Box 10, Folder 34)
  - Undergrad. Specials- research on Funding (Box 10, Folder 35)
  - Special Problems R Michael Wright 1970-1971 (Box 10, Folder 36)
  - Special Problems US 122 Dan T. Smith (1970-1971) (Box 10, Folder 37)
  - Undergraduate Special Program Administration Summer 1970 (Box 10, Folder 38)
  - Undergraduate Specials Course Administration 1971-1972 (Box 10, Folder 39)
  - Committee on Undergraduate Special Courses 1971-1972 (Box 10, Folder 40)
  - Unrest in the Academy: the Case of H. Bruce Frankin (problems) 1971-1972 (Box 10, Folder 41)
  - Undergraduate Special Program Summer Quarter 1971-1972 (Box 10, Folder 42)
  - Undergraduate Special Program Program Report to Jim Gibbs, 1972 (Box 10, Folder 43)
  - Handbook for UGS Courses- 1972 (Box 10, Folder 44)
  - UGS: Dean's Advisory C'ee: Members (Box 10, Folder 45)
  - Funding Undergraduate Specials (Box 10, Folder 46)
  - Winter Quarter 1972-1973 (Box 10, Folder 47)
  - Undergraduate Special Program Administration Spring 1972-1973 (Box 10, Folder 48)
  - Summer Quarter 1972-1973 (Box 10, Folder 49)
  - Registration in Absentia (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Undergraduate Special Committee 1972-1973 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - EDP Course Consumption Report 1972-1973 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Undergraduate Speical Program Course Administration 1973-1974 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - End Quarter Reports Fall 1981-1982 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Instructor's Handbook (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - End Quarter reports Spring 1981-1982 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - UGS Committee 1976-1977 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Undergraduate Special Program Administration 1977-1978 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Dean's Advisory Committee on Freshman Seminars (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Undergraduate Special Committee Minutes, 1977-1978 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Undergraduate Special Program Curriculum Gaps (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Undergrad Teaching Seminar Spring 1978 (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Undergraduate Special Program Administration 1978-1979 (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - UGS Procedures- History (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - September, 1979-1980 (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - Undergraduate Special Program, Dean's Advisory Committee, 1979-1980 (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - Undergraduate Special Program Admin. 1979-1980 (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - Report on FSSP 1981 (Box 11, Folder 19)
  - Undergraduate Special Program Admin. 1981-1982 (Box 11, Folder 20)
  - End Quarter Reports Winter 1982-1983 (Box 11, Folder 21)
  - Undergraduate Special Program Admin. 1982-1983 (Box 11, Folder 22)
  - Teaching Appointsments 1982-1983 (Box 11, Folder 23)
  - Undergraduate Special Program Joint Review (UGS, Frosh. Sems) 1982-1983 (Box 11, Folder 24)
  - C-US Program Reviews, 1982-1983 (Box 11, Folder 25)
  - Undergraduate Special Program Instructor Appreciation Events (Box 11, Folder 26)
  - Undergraduate Special Program Admin. 1983-1984 (Box 11, Folder 27)
  - Undergraduate Special Program, Registrar's Course Enrollment Stats. (Box 11, Folder 28)
  - End Quarter Grade Sheets Summer 1985 (Box 11, Folder 29)
  - UGS Handbook Revision 1985 (Box 11, Folder 30)
  - Class Lists- Spring 1985 (Box 11, Folder 31)
  - UGS Instructor's Payment Papers, fall 1985-1986 (Box 11, Folder 32)
  - Within Stanford From UGS 1985-1986 (Box 11, Folder 33)
  - Dean's Advisory Committee on UGS, 1985 (Box 11, Folder 34)
  - Undergraduate Special Program Handbook Revised 1985-1986 (Box 11, Folder 35)
  - Fall Quarter Catalogue Information (Box 11, Folder 36)
  - UGS Proposals, 1987-1988 (Box 11, Folder 37)
  - UGS Proposals, Winter 1988 (Box 11, Folder 38)
  - Repositurning: OG Studies (Box 11, Folder 39)
  - Old Catalogues (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - SWOPSI Catalogs 1969-1970 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - SWOPSI Catalogs 1971-1972 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - SWOPSI Catalogs 1972-1973 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - SWOPSI Catalogs 1973-1974 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - SWOPSI Catalogs 1974-1975 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - SWOPSI Catalogs 1975-1976 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - SWOPSI Catalogs 1976-1977 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - SWOPSI Catalogs 1977-1978 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - SWOPSI Catalogs 1978-1979 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - SWOPSI Catalogs 1979-1980 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - SWOPSI Catalogs Spring, Winter Fall 1980-1981 (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - SWOPSI Catalogs Fall 1981-1982 (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - SWOPSI Catalogs Winter 1981-1982 (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - SWOPSI Catalogs Spring 1981-1982 (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - SWOPSI Catalog Autumn 1982-1983 (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - SWOPSI Catalogs Winter 1982-1983 (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - SWOPSI Catalogs Spring 1982-1983 (Box 12, Folder 18)
  - SWOPSI Catalogs Autumn 1983-1984 (Box 12, Folder 19)
  - SWOPSI Catalogs Winter 1983-1984 (Box 12, Folder 20)
  - SWOPSI Catalogs Spring 1983-1984 (Box 12, Folder 21)
  - SWOPSI Catalogs Autumn 1984-1985 (Box 12, Folder 22)
  - SWOPSI Catalogs Winter Quarter 1984-1985 (Box 12, Folder 23)
  - SWOPSI Spring Catalogs 1984-1985 (Box 12, Folder 24)
  - SWOPSI Bulletin of Courses 1985-1986 (Box 12, Folder 25)
  - SWOP 101 The Utlilization and Disposal of Solid Waste, Summer 1971-1972 (Box 12, Folder 26)
  - SWOP 102 Practical Workshop in Electoral Politics, Fall 1971 (Box 12, Folder 27)
  - SWOP 103 Open Media: First Ammendment Access to TV, Fall 1971 (Box 12, Folder 28)
  - SWOP 104 Preschool Education and Developmental Psychology, Fall 1971 (Box 12, Folder 29)
  - SWOP 105 Aspects of Pollution Realted to the Oil Production Industry, Fall 1971 (Box 12, Folder 30)
  - SWOP 106 Research Workshop on Education and the Urban Poor, Fall 1971 (Box 12, Folder 31)
  - SWOP 107 Student Air Pollution Research, Fall 1971 (Box 12, Folder 32)
  - SWOP 108 Teaching and Learning in an Alternate High School, Fall 1971 (Box 12, Folder 33)
  - SWOP 109 +109B Peer Counseling Techniques in Drug Abuse Program, Fall 1971 (Box 12, Folder 34)
  - SWOP 110 Alternatives to Incarcertation in San Mateo County, Fall 1971 (Box 12, Folder 35)
  - SWOP 111 Unrest in the Acad., Winter 1971-1972 (Box 12, Folder 36)
  - SWOP 112 The Black College- Padulo, Winter 1972 (Box 12, Folder 37)
  - SWOP 113 Decision Making in Mental Health Lewis-Neufeld, Winter 1972 (Box 12, Folder 38)
  - 114 Financing Equal Education Opportunity Levin-Weiner, Winter 1972 (Box 12, Folder 39)
  - SWOP 115 Devel. of Child Advocacy Syst. for Santa Clara City: Burk-Lewis, Winter 1972 (Box 12, Folder 40)
  - SWOP 116 The Grand Jury: Kokjer, Tooby, Winter 1972 (Box 12, Folder 41)
  - SWOP 117 Juvenile Justice System, Winter 1972 (Box 12, Folder 42)
  - SWOP 118 New Strategies for Drug Abuse: Kaplan, Zarcone, Garfield, Winter 1972 (Box 12, Folder 43)
  - SWOP 119 Health Care Delivery Systems- Hobman- Marks, Winter 1972 (Box 12, Folder 44)
  - SWOP 120 Autistic and Sciz. Kids- Burk-Switzer, Winter 1972 (Box 12, Folder 45)
  - SWOP 120 Volunteer Work with Autistic and Schizophrenic Children, Leiderman, Switzer, Winter 1972 (Box 12, Folder 46)
  - SWOP 121 New Life Vocations Strain-Friedman, Winter 1972 (Box 12, Folder 47)
  - SWOP 122 The Housing System- Waldhorn, Winter 1972 (Box 12, Folder 48)
  - SWOP 123 Cognative and Social Development in Infants: Bloch, Hess, Winter 1972 (Box 12, Folder 49)
  - SWOP 124 A Cross-Cult Anal of Prostitution: McNeil, Rosaldo, Diebold, Winter 1972 (Box 12, Folder 50)
  - SWOP 125 Intercommunalism Theory and Pracrice Keilch, Winter 1972 (Box 12, Folder 51)
  - SWOP 126 Who Owns the Land S.F. Peninsula, Ransom, Drekmeier, Winter 1972 (Box 12, Folder 52)
  - SWOP 127 Student Air Pollution Blake, Perkell, Winter 1972 (Box 12, Folder 53)
  - SWOP 153- Children and the State, Lewis, Winter 1972 (Box 12, Folder 54)
  - SWOP 128 Community Information Systems Breed, Spring 1972 (Box 12, Folder 55)
  - SWOP 129 Half Moon Bay Henson, Mayer, Spring 1972 (Box 12, Folder 56)
  - SWOP 130 Child Development Nelson-Gottschalk, Spring 1972 (Box 12, Folder 57)
  - SWOP 131 Cheap, Good, Food, Pinfield, Klevansky, Frederick, Spring 1972 (Box 12, Folder 58)
  - SWOP 132 Women in the University HEW Bem. Sloan, Spring 1972 (Box 12, Folder 59)
  - SWOP 133 Techno. and Nonviol. Ethic Medius, Kaehler, Spring 1972 (Box 12, Folder 60)
  - SWOP 134 Comm. Atts. on Drug Abuse McGann, Hannay, Spring 1972 (Box 12, Folder 61)
  - SWOP 135 Third World Dependency Carnoy, Girlings, Schmidts, Spring 1972 (Box 12, Folder 62)
  - SWOP 100 Computer Revolution, Fall 1972-1973 (Box 12, Folder 63)
  - SWOP 109 Peer Counselling in Drug Abuse Program V.J. D'Andrea MD, Fall 1972 (Box 12, Folder 64)
  - SWOP 136 Peru-Planning for Development, Daetz, Ruiz, Fall 1972 (Box 12, Folder 65)
  - SWOP 137 Changing the Penal System Oki, Mack, fALL 1972 (Box 12, Folder 66)
  - SWOP 139, Rape, Stone, Dana Lou, Weigent, Fall 1972 (Box 12, Folder 67)
  - SWOP 141 Alternatives to Incarceration in Santa Clara County, Lynn, Fall 1972 (Box 12, Folder 68)
  - SWOP 142 Child Care for the Future, Taylor, Peterson, Fall 1972 (Box 12, Folder 69)
  - SWOP 143 Varsity Athletics, the Black Community and Stanford. Organ, Fall 1972 (Box 12, Folder 70)
  - SWOP 144 Farmworkers etc., Tramutt, Horsho, Fall 1972 (Box 12, Folder 71)
  - SWOP 145 Suburban Stranglehold on the Central City, Waldhorn, Fall 1972 (Box 12, Folder 72)
  - SWOP 146 Grading System at Stanford, Mitchell, Fall 1972 (Box 12, Folder 73)
  - SWOP 147 Student task Force on Education at Stanford, Appel, et. al, Fall 1972 (Box 12, Folder 74)
  - SWOP 156 Locating and Communicating Models of Social Change, Growald, Fall 1972 (Box 12, Folder 75)
  - SWOP 159 Irene Soledad Letters, Fall 1972 (Box 12, Folder 76)
  - SWOP 149 International Community and Psychological Growth, Leland Wendel, Winter 1973 (Box 12, Folder 77)
  - SWOP 151 Surburban Land Use Control McCaugherty, Ayers, Fink, Winter 1973 (Box 12, Folder 78)
  - SWOP 155 Playing/Learning Environment for Children, Mann, Winter 1973 (Box 12, Folder 79)
  - SWOP 157 Reconstruction in Indo-China, Textor, Winter 1973 (Box 12, Folder 80)
  - SWOP 158 New Options the Future of Legal Profession, Wheeler, Mellberg, Winter 1973 (Box 12, Folder 81)
  - SWOP 138 Approaches to Learnings Jim Kerr, John Junkerman, Spring 1973 (Box 12, Folder 82)
  - SWOP 150 Influence of Defense Industry on the Midpeninsula, Collis, Srping 1973 (Box 12, Folder 83)
  - SWOP 154 Child Care Socialization or Freedom? Bonham, Spring 1973 (Box 12, Folder 84)
  - SWOP 159 Soledad Teaching Project Gage and Others, Spring 1973 (Box 12, Folder 85)
  - SWOP 160 Should BART Come Down the Peninsula? Lewin, Spring 1973 (Box 12, Folder 86)
  - SWOP 161 Project Synergy Exploring and Counseling, etc., Long and Levine Spring 1973 (Box 12, Folder 87)
  - SWOP 163 the Women Question through Film, Wright and Others, Spring 1973 (Box 12, Folder 88)
  - SWOP 164 New Options: Alternatives in the Health Care Professions Mease, Spring 1973 (Box 12, Folder 89)
  - SWOP 165 Stanford Foster Care Project for Juvenile Offenders Mann, Spring 1973 (Box 12, Folder 90)
  - SWOP 166 Macroanalysis Seminar Newton and Smith, Spring 1973 (Box 12, Folder 91)
  - SWOP 109 Peer Counseling in Drop In Centers Fall 1973 (Box 12, Folder 92)
  - SWOP 120 Volunteer Work with Autistic and Schizophrenic Children Fall 1973 (Box 12, Folder 93)
  - SWOP 161 Synergy Fall 1973 (Box 12, Folder 94)
  - SWOP 142 Child Care: Ways of Growing Fall 1973 (Box 12, Folder 95)
  - SWOP 148 Problems of Aging in Santa Clara County, Immorlica, Charlotte (Box 12, Folder 96)
  - SWOP 167 The Junkie Next Door McDaniel, Spring 1973 (Box 12, Folder 97)
  - SWOP 152 Preservation of Wild Lands Farrell 1973 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - SWOP 153 Children and the State Fall 1973 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - SWOP 168 Working in Behavior Modification Classroom Fall 1973 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - SWOP 169 The Jesus Movement from the Inside Fall 1973 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - SWOP 170 Criminal Activity on the Farm Fall 1973 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - SWOP 171 The Administration of Justice Fall 1973 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - SWOP 172 The United States and Southeast Asia, Fall 1973 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - SWOP 173 What's so Special About Alternative Schools Fall 1973 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - SWOP 174 Workshop on Women Fall 1973 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - SWOP 175 Case Studies in California Land Use, Fall 1973 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - SWOP 176 The Making of a Newspaper Fall 1973 (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - SWOP 177 History and the Old, Fall 1973 (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - SWOP 178 International Political Prisoners Fall 1973 (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - SWOP 179 Planning for the Future Fall 1973 (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - SWOP 180 Elementary Language Arts Program Fall 1973 (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - SWOP 182 New Towns: Corporate or Community Control Fall 1973 (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - SWOP 183 Workshop on Proposition 20 Fall 1973 (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - SWOP 100 Abused and Neglected Child and the Law Fall 1974 (Box 13, Folder 18)
  - SWOP 101 Behavior Modification Fall 1974 (Box 13, Folder 19)
  - SWOP 109 Peer Couseling- Bridge Fall 1974 (Box 13, Folder 20)
  - SWOP 120 Autistic/Schizophrenic Children Fall 1974 (Box 13, Folder 21)
  - SWOP 142 Child Care: Ways of Growing Fall 1974 (Box 13, Folder 22)
  - SWOP 155 Bicycles Fall 1974 (Box 13, Folder 23)
  - SWOP 161 Synergy, Fall 1974 (Box 13, Folder 24)
  - SWOP 168: Behavoir Modification in Handicapped Children Fall 1974 (Box 13, Folder 25)
  - SWOP 174 Workshop on Women Fall 1974 (Box 13, Folder 26)
  - SWOP 174B Workshop on Women Spring 1974 (Box 13, Folder 27)
  - SWOP 190 Women and the Law Fall 1974 (Box 13, Folder 28)
  - SWOP 192 Emotionally Disabled in the Community Fall 1974 (Box 13, Folder 29)
  - SWOP 197 Young Outlaws Fall 1974 (Box 13, Folder 30)
  - SWOP 198: Evangelical Politcs, Fall 1974 (Box 13, Folder 31)
  - SWOP 173 What's So Special About Alternative Schools Winter 1974 (Box 13, Folder 32)
  - SWOP 109 Peer Counseling Spring 1974 (Box 13, Folder 33)
  - SWOP 109B Peer Counseling in Drop In Centers Winter 1974 (Box 13, Folder 34)
  - SWOP 120B Volunteer Work with Autistic and Schizophrenic Children, Winter 1974 (Box 13, Folder 35)
  - SWOP 142B Child Care: Ways of Growing Winter 1974 (Box 13, Folder 36)
  - SWOP 153B Children and the State: Winter 1974 (Box 13, Folder 37)
  - SWOP 168B Working in Behavior Mod. Classroom Winter 1974 (Box 13, Folder 38)
  - SWOP 169B The Jesus Movement from the Inside, Winter 1974 (Box 13, Folder 39)
  - SWOP 171B The Administration of Justice, Winter 1974 (Box 13, Folder 40)
  - SWOP 174B Workshop on Women Winter 1974 (Box 13, Folder 41)
  - SWOP 177B History and the Old, Winter 1974 (Box 13, Folder 42)
  - SWOP 181 Students and University Governance Winter 1974 (Box 13, Folder 43)
  - SWOP 182B New Towns: Corporate or Community Control Winter 1974 (Box 13, Folder 44)
  - SWOP 184 US Foreign Policy/ in Latin America/ American Worker Winter 1974 (Box 13, Folder 45)
  - SWOP 185 Design for Alternative Lifestyles Winter 1974 (Box 13, Folder 46)
  - SWOP 187 Commuting- Why Not Carpools? Winter 1974 (Box 13, Folder 47)
  - SWOP 188 Juveniles and the Courts Winter 1974 (Box 13, Folder 48)
  - SWOP 190 Women and the Law Winter 1974 (Box 13, Folder 49)
  - SWOP 191 Alcohol, Dope and Other Hangups/ Coping Behavior Winter 1974 (Box 13, Folder 50)
  - SWOP 193 Latin America in the US Press Winter 1974 (Box 13, Folder 51)
  - SWOP 186 Movements and Minorities in the Movies Winter 1974 (Box 13, Folder 52)
  - US in Vietnam (Box 13, Folder 53)
  - SWOP 120C Autistic/ Schizo./ Children Spring 1974 (Box 13, Folder 54)